http://www.ghilliesuitshop.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyGhillieSuitShop.com is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and to protecting any personal information provided online, therefore we offer the following privacy policy.Basic confidentiality policyIt is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and email address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you supply is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to respond to a request or to process your order).We do send occasional emails to our customers with promotions and/or special offers. You may opt out of these emails at any time.Non release of informationPersonal information will not be released to any third parties except for the purpose for which you provide the information (such as confirming an address for credit card processing or order fulfillment). We do not provide or sell information to third parties for any other reason.Statistics TrackingWhile our website does track statistics about visits to our website such as daily number of visitors, most popular pages and referrals to our website, the statistics contain no personal information, and are used strictly internally to provide better service.Secure Online OrderingWe take security seriously as our website offers secure ordering for your protection. Our Store uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer and AOL's browser so that only GhillieSuitShop.com can read a buyer's personal information. All account information submitted to us is safely isolated from unauthorized Internet access. Credit cards are not charged until the day the items are shipped.Your credit card information is being requested and used by a credit card processing company for the purpose of processing your purchase transaction. We do not use, store or have access to your credit card information.
Featured Products
Stinger Spin Ssp60/802mh Combo for Fishing - GhillieSuitShop
